Guide to the National Organization for Women, New York City Chapter (NOW-NYC) Records TAM.106
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Photographs, Negatives, and Slides, 1967-2011; 1984-1989, 2002; 6.96 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 4 manuscript boxes, a flat box, and 2 oversized flat boxes
  This series consists of black and white photographs; color photographs; negatives; contact sheets; and slides. This series contains portraits of NOW-NYC staff and the Board of Directors; and publicity photographs. This series also includes photo documentation of campaigns, events, meetings, and rallies that members of the Reproductive Rights; Reproduction and its Control; ERA; and Rape Prevention Committees participated in. The series also includes photo documentation of marches on behalf of local and national electoral campaigns; NOW-NYC member participation in National NOW conferences; the Susan B. Anthony Awards and the Women of Power & Influence Awards; protests and demonstrations such as the anti-trafficking protest held in Times Square; and social gatherings. Both physical and digital photographs are included in this series.
  Materials in this series are arranged alphabetically by title and then chronologically, when applicable.
  - 16 mm: NOW Wash., June 29, 1982 (Box 40)
  - 16 mm: Approach, undated (Box 40)
  - 16 mm: Crowd, undated (Box 40)
  - 24 Hour Watch for the ERA, August 26, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - A.A.A. Pregnancy Problem Clinic [Contact Sheet, Print and Negatives], 1986 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Abortion March -- New York Foley Square, July 5, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Abortion March -- Washington Press Conference, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Abortion and Operation Rescue, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Abortion and Operation Rescue -- Dobbs Ferry, Dec 1988 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Abortion and Operation Rescue -- Planned Parenthood, undated (Box 43, Folder 41-42)
  - ["Abortion and Operation Rescue -- Planned Parenthood" -- Negatives], undated (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Abortion and Operation Rescue -- Schwartz Clinic, May 6, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Abortion and Operation Rescue -- Queens Clinic, undated (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Abortion and Operation Rescue -- Queens Clinic, undated (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - ["Abortion and Operation Rescue -- -Queens Clinic" -- Negatives], undated (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Abortion Protest -- Bush, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Abortion Protest -- Saint Patrick's, February 1989 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - "April March Against the War" [Photograph by Judith Brown], [1970] (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Art, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Art -- Sojourner Truth and Esther Morris, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Arts Committee, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Images, circa 1970-1984 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - [Awards-Others], 1987, 1990, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Bella Abzug, 1981, undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors [Polaroid Portraits], 1982 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Brian Palmer Photos -- Operation Rescue, Undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Celebrate Suffrage Fundraiser, Summer 1994 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Cherry Hill Demonstration, undated (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Committee Members and Others [Polaroid Portraits], Undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Deceased Women Post-Abortion, undated (Box 33, Folder 3, Box Shared Tamiment OS009, Folder 1)
    CONTENT WARNING: These photographs contains depictions of both nudity and death.
  - Demonstrations Against Circuit City and George W. Bush, circa 2000s (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Demonstration at Fake Abortion Clinic "Options", July 30, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - [Demonstration at Fake Abortion Clinic "Options" -- Negatives], July 30, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Demonstration -- "Divorce: American Style" at Court Building, 1985? (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - [Demonstration -- "Divorce: American Style" -- Negatives], 1985? (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Demonstration -- Photos by Gina Salth, January 22, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - [Demonstration -- Photos by Gina Salth -- Negatives], January 22, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Elayne Snyder, 1974 (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - Election Eve Party at NOW-1984/Betty Friedan on NOW's "Birthday" October 1984 (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - Elections -- Officers, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - Endorsement, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - ERA Campaigns, June 1982, Undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - ERA Committee -- "NOW Goes to Virginia for the ERA" [Photograph by Jean Vertheim], January 21, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - ERA Committee -- ERA March, Chicago, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - ERA Vigil Women's Equality Day, August 22, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Fannie Lou Hamer Freedom High School Young Woman's Club, circa 2002 (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - First National Women's Conference, 1977 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Fundraiser, August 26, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Fundraiser, July 17 and 28 [year unknown] (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Fundraiser at First Women's Bank, 1984 (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - Gay Pride, March 1989 (Box 43, Folder 29, Box 143, Folder 21)
  - [Gay Pride? -- Washington D.C.], 1993 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - [Gay Pride? -- Washington D.C. -- Negatives], 1993 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Gloria Jacobs -- New York State Marriage and Divorce Task Force, undated (Box 143, Folder 22)
  - [Group Portraits], 1994, undated (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Hillary Clinton Event at Barnard College, 2008; TW_TAM_106_ER_4
  - Insurance Demonstration, undated (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - ["Insurance Demonstration" -- Negatives], undated (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Jerry Skohle, August 22, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - ["Jerry Skohle" -- Negatives], August 22, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Labor Day, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - "Let's Stop the Violence" [Photographs by Edye Falencki], 1989 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Lobby Day, 1989 (Box 143, Folder 23)
  - Lobbying -- Albany, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Mademoiselle Magazine Awards: Anne Grant, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - "March for Women's Equality/Women's Lives" [Contact Sheets and Prints], April 9, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Matthea Marquart, 2002 (Box 143, Folder 24)
  - [Miscellaneous Conferences], undated (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - [Miscellaneous Demonstrations and Rallies -- Dated], late 1970s - early 1990s (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - [Miscellaneous Demonstrations and Rallies -- Undated] (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - [Miscellaneous Demonstrations and Rallies -- Undated] (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - [Miscellaneous Demonstrations and Rallies -- Undated -- Contacts with Negatives] (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - [Miscellaneous Demonstrations and Rallies -- Dated and Undated], 1980-1991, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - [Miscellaneous Individuals], 1979, undated (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - [Miscellaneous Marches -- Dated], 1978 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - [Miscellaneous Marches -- Undated] (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - National and Regional NOW -- National NOW Convention, Miami, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - National and Regional NOW -- National NOW Convention, San Antonio, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - National NOW Conference, 1980, 1982-1984 (Box 43, Folder 47, Box 143, Folder 25-27)
  - National NOW Conference -- Denver, CO -- March and Rally, June 1986 (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - ["National NOW Conference -- Denver, CO -- March and Rally" Negatives], June 1986 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - National NOW Conference -- Miami, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - National NOW Conference -- New Orleans, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - ["National NOW Conference- New Orleans" -- Negatives], 1985 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - National NOW Conference -- Washington D.C., 1983 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - National NOW Conference Rally to Overturn the Gag Rule, July 1991 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - ["National NOW Conference Rally to Overturn the Gag Rule" -- Negatives], July 1991 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - Negatives -- Rallies and Meetings, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - NOW Direct Market Training Program, February 4, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - NOW-NYS Conference Includes: Noreen Connell, Barbara Ehrenreich, Judy Goldsmith, Carol Bellamy, Janice LaPorche, Muriel Fox, Bella Abzug, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - NOW-NYC April Membership Meeting, 2002 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - NOW-NYC Election, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - NOW-NYC Elections Includes: Jennifer Brown, Carolyn Chambers, Kelli Conlin, Ann Colona, Trish Bellae, Francois Jacobsohn, Karen Rood, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - ["NOW-NYC Elections 1988" -- Negatives] (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - NOW-NYC Elections Includes: S. Hartnett, S.Spaulding, Jennifer Brown, V. Partridge, D. Welsh, N. Northup, M. Williams, L. Baldwin, S. Lombard, M. Giomonsis [?], 1985 (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - NOW State Conference, undated (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - NYU NOW Meeting, 2002 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - [People-Individuals] "B" Includes Jennifer Brown and Carol Bellamy, undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - [People Individuals-"B"-negatives], undated (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - [People-Individuals] "C" Includes Noreen Connell, Christine Craft, 1986, undated (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - [People-Individuals] "D", 1967, 1980, undated (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - [People-Individuals] "E" Includes Barbara Ehrenreich, undated (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - [People-Individuals] "F" Includes New York Councilwoman M. Friedlander, Muriel Fox, Betty Friedan, 1981, undated (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - [People-Individuals] "G" Includes Judy Goldsmith, undated (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - [People-Individuals] "H" Includes M. Hoffman, undated (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - [People-Individuals] "J", 1989, undated (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - [People-Individuals] "K", 1981 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - [People-Individuals] "L" Includes Ladies Against Women, Susan Lombard, undated (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - [People-Individuals] "M", 1988, undated (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - [People-Individuals] "N", undated (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - [People-Individuals] "O", undated (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - [People-Individuals] "P", undated (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - [People-Individuals] "Q/R" Includes Sally Ride, 1987, undated (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - [People-Individuals] "S", undated (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - [People-Individuals] "T", undated (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - [People-Individuals] "U", undated (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - [People-Individuals] "V", undated (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - [People-Individuals] "W", 1981, 1988, undated (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Political Figures and Celebrities, 1981, 1984, 1989, undated (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Political Figures and Celebrities, undated (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Press Conference with Congressman Anthony Weiner, 2002 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Press Conference in Support of Liz Holtzman on the Steps of Supreme Court Building, December 1987 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - [Press Conference in Support of Liz Holtzman on the Steps of Supreme Court Building -- Negatives], December 1987 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Pro-Choice Rally Washington D.C., November 12, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Rally at Bryant Park, NYC-NY Pro-Choice Coalition, January 22, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Focus 15 Slide Show, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Rehnquist Rally, Aug 1986 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Reproduction and its Control Committee -- Pro-Choice March, March 1972, N.Y.C. [Includes baby Sleeping in Stroller with Pin, "I'm Not Going to Give Up My Right to Choose"] [35 mm negative] (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- 9th anniversary of Roe v. Wade [Credit Unknown], January 22, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- 9th anniversary of Roe v. Wade [Photographs by Tom Beckett], January 22, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Reproduction and its Control Committee -- Abortion Picket Line, June 14, 1974 [Contact Sheet] (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Abortion Teach-In [Photographs by Jean Wertheim], January 21, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Demonstration, April 1979 [Color Slides by Linda Grishman] (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- St. Patrick's Cathedral Demonstration [Contact Sheet Carin Drescher-Marx], 1976 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Staten Island Demonstration [Contact Sheets, Negatives; Credit Unknown], 1981 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Reproductive Rights March -- Fifth Avenue, Cherry Hill Demonstration, St. Patrick's Demonstration, undated (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - [Reproductive Rights March -- Negatives], undated (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Saks Fifth Avenue Protest, 1996 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Slides -- 2nd Select Action, Ganley River, undated (Box 40)
  - Slides -- Mary Kay, Rosie the Riveter, May 1981 - June 1981 (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW, undated (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW Cherry Hill N.U., undated (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW Copies, undated (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW Election Campaign Meeting, undated (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW Labor Day, 1983 (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW Labor Day, undated (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW Member Meeting, undated (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW PSA, undated (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW Rally, July 1981 (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW Rally, July 1981 (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW SF, August 1982 (Box 40)
  - Slides -- NOW WomanPower PAC, undated (Box 40)
  - Slides -- Reproductive Rights Coalition March, 1981 (Box 40)
  - Slides -- Reproductive Rights March, 1981 (Box 40)
  - Slides -- Slides found loose in box, undated (Box 40)
  - Slides -- Unidentified shoots, #1-10, undated (Box 40)
  - Street Fair, 1988, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Stop Human Trafficking Event, 2007; TW_TAM_106_ER_5
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1980, 1985, 1988, 1989, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - ["Susan B. Anthony Awards"- 1985 Negatives] (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 2002 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 2009; TW_TAM_106_ER_6
  - Sweatshop Rally, 2002 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified NOW-NYC Events, 1984, 1998-1999, 2001, 2010-2012, undated (Box 144, Folder 8-13)
  - Unidentified Photograph [Johnny Cash and Unidentified Woman], undated (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - [Unidentified Events -- Dated], 1979-1992 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - [Unidentified Events-- Undated] (Box 44, Folder 17-21)
  - [Unidentified Events -- Undated -- Negatives with Prints] (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Viacom Protest, 2007; TW_TAM_106_ER_7
  - Vienna Philharmonic Protest, 2002 (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - [Woman holding "Never Again" sign, photographer Dianna Wade, oversized], 1974 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - "Woman Power is Too Good to Waste" [Photographs by Marilyn Schwartz], undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Womanpower PAC 1982 Election Campaign (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - "Women March for Equality," August 26, 1971 [Contact Sheets, Bettye Lane Photographer] (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Women Photographer's NOW Opening, June 1986 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Women of Power & Influence Awards, 2004; TW_TAM_106_ER_8
  - Women of Power & Influence Awards, 2010; TW_TAM_106_ER_9
  - "Women's Equality Day", August 26, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Women's Equality Day, undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Women's Equality Day, Voter Registration Drive, Truth Square Anti-Reagan Demonstration, and Pay Equity, August 27, 1984 and undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Women's Equality Day Rally at the New York Public Library, August 26, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Women's Truth Squad, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - World March of Women in Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - "Witness Women's Lives" -- Pro-Choice Demonstration at Saint Patrick's, June 1985 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - ["Witness Women's Lives" -- Pro-Choice Demonstration at Saint Patrick's], June 1985 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Series IX: Artifacts, Ephemera, and Graphic Materials, 1970-2017; 12.53 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes, a half manuscript box, 3 flat boxes, 15 oversized flat boxes, and 6 flat-file-folders
  This series includes NOW-NYC artifacts, ephemera, and graphic materials. Materials include protest signs and fabric banners whose topics include reproductive rights and the Equal Rights Amendment; the 1984 Presidential Election, specifically anti-Ronald Reagan and pro-Walter Mondale and Geraldine Ferraro; sexual discrimination and domestic violence; gay rights; and opposition to societal beauty standards. This series also contains posters and templates for protest signs; buttons, name tags, and t-shirts; and paper materials including essays, sheet music, cartoons, and greeting cards.
  Materials in this series are arranged alphabetically by format.
  - Balloons -- "Ratify the ERA," "A Day for Women's Rights -- Ratify the ERA 8/22/77," "I Love Equality / NOW-NYC / Boycott States that Have not Ratified the ERA", 1977 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Banners -- Abortion, undated (Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Banners -- Equal Rights Divorce Reform Bill, undated (Flat-file-folder 1)
    Homemade banner made by members of the NOW Marriage and Divorce Committee, likely of the New York City Chapter, measuring 51.5 inches by 24 inches.
  - Banners -- Equal Rights Amendment, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 023, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Banners -- "ERA-YES", undated (Box Shared Tamiment 194, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Banners -- NOW-NYC, undated (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Banners -- "PARTNERSHIP IN MARRIAGE", undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Banners -- We Won't Go Back, undated (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - Banners -- Woman Power Vote, undated (Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Buttons, undated (Box 37, Folder 1, Box 158, Folder 8-11)
  - Campaign Ephemera, 1990-2016 (Box 105, Folder 10-11)
  - Cartoons -- Lady Liberty by Ann Leggett, undated (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Cartoons -- Lady Liberty by Sandi Marks, 1981 (Box Shared Tamiment 208, Folder 9)
  - Cartoons -- "Potluck in the Park", undated (Box Shared Tamiment 208, Folder 3)
  - Cartoons -- Untitled, undated (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Cartoons -- Untitled Drawings by Melina Spera, undated (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Clippings (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Cross-Stitch Patterns -- "Liberté Egalité Sororité", undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Ephemera, undated (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Ephemera -- NOW-NYC Tote bag, undated (Box 94)
  - Ephemera -- NOW-NYC Women of Power and Influence Award Magnifying Glass, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Ephemera -- Pink Kerchief, undated (Box 94)
  - Film Strips and Film Containers -- "Women Now Pt. 1" and "Women Now Pt. 2" by Feminist Productions Inc. Babylon, NY, undated (Box 108)
  - Graphics, undated (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Graphics -- The NOW York Times, The Trulytzer Prize, Women's Equality Day Proclamation, 1971-1981 (Box Shared Tamiment OS009)
  - Greeting Cards - Main Line Company Feminist Greeting Cards, 1985 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Greeting Cards -- NOW-NYC Holiday Card, undated (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Hat and Visor -- "Carol Bellamy Election Day Team and "NOW/PAC Woman" (Box 108)
  - Lace -- Pieces, 1977-1979 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Name Tag -- "Focus 15: Yolanda Bako", 1975 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Paper Materials -- Women's History Series, 1974-1981 (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - Paper Materials -- Women's Resource Guide to NYC by NOW-NYC, undated (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - Paper Materials -- NOW Handouts, 1991, undated (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Paper Materials -- NOW-NYC Calendar Pages, undated (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Paper Materials -- Proclamation from Governor of New York State for Susan B. Anthony Day, Women's Equality Week, Women's Equality Day, ERA Countdown Day, International Women's Day, and Resolution, 1978-1984 (Box Shared Tamiment 194, Folder 5)
  - Paper Materials -- Proclamations of Women's Equality Day and ERA Countdown Day from the Mayor of New York State, 1981, 1982 (Box Shared Tamiment 194, Folder 6)
  - Paper Materials -- Various NOW Documents [Includes Press Releases; "National Organization for Women: Woman Power Project" Report on Referral System; NOW-NYC Training Manual; "NOW-NYC A Case Study"; Workshop Materials, circa 1977-1995 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Paper Materials -- We Were Militants Draft by Charlotte H. Peaslee, 1970 (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Posters -- "Doctor Ima Fraud -- Lay Analyst", 1971 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Posters -- Educational Action Conference, 1974 (Flat-file-folder 4 Right)
  - Posters -- ERA, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Posters -- Feminist Bureau of Investigations (FBI): The Most Wanted Men for Offenses Against Women, 1974 (Flat-file-folder 3 Right)
  - Posters -- It's All Right to Be a Woman Theatre, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 208, Folder 2)
  - Posters -- Sex Discrimination (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Posters -- 'Tis the Season to be Equal, circa December 1971 (Flat-file-folder TBD)
    Large scale drawing of holiday poster or card depicting a townhouse facade with Shirley Chisholm for President sticker affixed to top left corner.
  - Posters -- Urban Woman Conference (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Posters -- Women's Rights Day, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Posters -- Women's Sexuality Conference (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Program -- "How Long Must Women Wait for Liberty? New York and the Woman's Suffrage Movement, 1848-1920", 1995 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Program -- Lillian Roberts Tribute, 1981 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Protest Pennants, 1980, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Protest Signs, undated (Box 33, Folder 7-12, Box 98, Item 1-10, Box 153, Folder 19, Box 154, Folder 2-7)
  - Protest Signs -- 1984 Presidential Election (Box 96, Folder 1-2, Box 100, Item 6-15, Box 154, Folder 8-10)
  - Protest Signs -- Abortion, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 3-4, Box 97, Item 4-9, Box 99, Item 1-43, Box 100, Item 1-5, Box 155, Folder 1-2)
  - Protest Signs -- Anti-Ronald Reagan, circa 1981-1984 (Box 97, Item 12-13, Box 100, Item 16-33, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Protest Signs -- Anti-Domestic Violence, undated (Box 98, Item 15)
  - Protest Signs -- Dominique Strauss-Kahn, undated (Box 96, Folder 5, Box 155, Folder 3-5)
  - Protest Signs -- ERA, undated (Box 98, Item 11-14)
  - Protest Signs -- Gay Rights, undated (Box 96, Folder 6-9, Box 98, Item 15-19, Box 155, Folder 6-8)
  - Protest Signs -- NOW Elections, undated (Box 97, Item 10-11, Box 98, Item 20-22)
  - Protest Signs -- Rape, undated (Box 91)
  - Protest Signs -- Register to Vote, undated (Box 155, Folder 10-11)
  - Protest Signs -- Sex Discrimination, undated (Box 98, Item 23-29)
  - Protest Signs -- Societal Beauty Standards, undated (Box 91)
  - Protest Signs -- Women's March on Washington, 2017 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Protest Signs -- Women's Rights, undated (Box 97, Item 1-3, Box 98, Item 30-34)
  - Protest T-Shirts, undated (Box 85)
  - Sash -- March for Women's Lives, undated (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Sheet Music -- "Liberation Now!: Theme of Women's Liberation", 1970 (Box 107, Folder 5, Box 145)
  - Songbook -- Nasty Women Songbook, 2016 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Stamps and Prescription Bottle -- "ERA YES" Stamps and Prescription Bottle with Label "FOR EQUALITY", undated (Box 108)
  - Stickers, undated (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Stickers -- Reproductive Rights Committee Bumper Stickers and "STOP Violence Against Women" Stickers, [1977-1979] (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Stickers -- This Promotes Women Hating, undated (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Transparencies -- NOW, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - T-Shirts -- Anti-Donald Trump, undated (Box 85)
  - T-Shirts -- ERA, 1981-1982 (Box 94)
  - T-Shirts -- NOW Kid's Shirt, undated (Box 85)
  - T-Shirts -- NOW-NYC Adult Shirts, undated (Box 85)
  - T-Shirts -- "We'll Remember Each November ERA YES," "Keep Your Laws Off My Body," and "Pro Choice NOW", undated (Box 37, Folder 3-5)
- Series X: Our North American Foremothers Documentary, 1970-1984; 5.55 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes, a record carton, a custom box, a flat box, an oversized flat box, and a flat-file-folder